'use strict';

const questionSTORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which is the smallest unit of data in a quantum system?',
        answers: [
            'bit',
            'qubit',
            'byte',
            'micro-data',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'qubit',
    }, {
        question: 'Why is Quantum Computing different?',
        answers: [
            'Quantum is dangerous',
            'Tedious',
            'Superposition',
            'IBM invented',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Superposition',
    }, {
        question: 'What is a superposition state?',
        answers: [
            'Multiple states at the same time',
            'One state forever',
            'No states at any point',
            'An empowered state',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Multiple states at the same time',
    }, {
        question: 'If classical systems consist of logic gates, which gate do quantum systems contain?',
        answers: [
            'Zero Gates',
            'Qugates',
            'Super Gates',
            'Quantum Gates',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Quantum Gates',
    }, {
        question: 'What takes place after a qubit is observed?',
        answers: [
            'Wave Function Collapse',
            'Particle Disruption',
            'Quantum Explosion',
            'Nothing',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Wave Function Collapse',
    }, {
        question: 'Who is considered the Father of Quantum Physics?',
        answers: [
            'Isaac Newton',
            'Max Planck',
            'Henry L. Quantum',
            'Thomas Jefferson',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Max Planck',
    }, {
        question: 'Which is considered the "God Particle"?',
        answers: [
            'The Atom',
            'Gluons',
            'Gravitation',
            'Higgs boson',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Higgs boson',
    }, {
        question: 'What makes the God Particle unique?',
        answers: [
            'It gives other Particles Mass',
            'First historical reference in the Bible',
            'Theorized to have created life',
            'It lives in the sky',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'It gives other Particles Mass',
    }, {
        question: 'Which is a phenomenon where a particle can phase through a barrier?',
        answers: [
            'Teleportation',
            'Superposition',
            'Quantum Tunneling',
            'the Quantum displacement',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'Quantum Tunneling',
    }, {
        question: 'Which is an object in quantum physics?',
        answers: [
            'Particles',
            'Waves',
            'Neither',
            'All of the above',
        ],
        rightAnswer: 'All of the above',
    }];